https://www.wiggys.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
Search
FREE SHIPPING Learn More!
Ponchos & Poncho Liners
Rain Gear (Waterproof)
Popular Topics
Why Lamilite?
vacuum packed sleeping bags
Subscribe to Wiggy's Newsletter » Receive updates about new products, specials, and learn about insulation technology
Name
Email
Having trouble receiving our newsletter? Resubscribe Here (Opens in a new window).
Wiggy's, Inc. Privacy Policy
Wiggy's, Inc. Privacy Policy has been developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the finest quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our customers. The Policy guides how we collect, store and use information about customers and prospects, and it will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices, and our customers' changing needs.
Our Policy recognizes that personal data deserves protection. Personal data includes, for example: e-mail addresses, billing information, employment status and "click stream" data that tracks visitor activity on a our website or online services. Our Policy provides the following:
1. Notice
We will inform you about why we are collecting Personal Data and how we intend to use it. We need to collect and store your name, address, and other basic personal data, for example, to provide you with the product or service you requested, as well as for billing & shipping purposes.
2. Sharing
From time to time, we are approached by companies and organizations that have a product or service that they believe may be of interest to you. Wiggy's has never in the past, nor will we in the future, share your personal data with any company, individual, or organization that is not affiliated with Wiggy's, Inc.
3. Security
We will maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of your personal data on our premises.
4. Review & Correction
We are continuing to enhance our procedures to enable you to review and correct, upon request, the personal information we collect from you. To modify this information, you may create an account on this Site and update your info accordingly. You may also call us at +1 (866) 411-6465 to update or remove any of your personal information.
Policy Details
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Wiggy's Inc. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the wiggys.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Wiggy's Inc..
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, or fill out a form. Users may be asked for, as appropriate: name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. Credit Card numbers are never stored on this website. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities, such as completing an order or receiving communications from us.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and basic technical information about the User's means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. We use this information only for the purposes of better understanding the type of technology that's accessing our site so that we can better serve site visitors.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance & speed up User experience. A User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track essential information, such as whether you are logged into our site or have added any items to your cart. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. Primarily, limiting cookies may impede your ability to create & use an account on our website, or to add items to your cart & check out. If you prefer to block cookies entirely, you may always call us at +1 (866) 411-6465 to place or complete any order.
How we use collected information
Wiggy's Inc. may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
To improve customer service Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs. Without a phone number or email address, we cannot contact you. We will only use this info for the purpose of contacting you regarding your orders or inquiries.
To process payments We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide complete & ship your order.
To send periodic emails We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others, ever. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners for the sole purposes outlined above. We occasionally use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or shipping products to you. We may share your information with these third parties only for those limited purposes, and only if you have given us appropriate permission. In these cases, we will only share the necessary information to complete the requested service, and nothing more.
Changes to this privacy policy
Wiggy's Inc. has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time, as needed to comply with regulations and new technologies. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Questions & Comments?
Wiggy's, Inc. Privacy Policy has been developed out of respect for the privacy preferences and choices of our customers and prospects. We have established procedures to ensure that every reasonable effort is made to address your concerns. If you have questions or comments about our Privacy Policy, please send them to me directly at:
Wiggy's Inc.PO Box 2124Grand Junction, CO 81502
You can also email me at: wiggys@wiggys.com or call me at +1 (866) 411-6465
Jerry Wigutow, President
This document was last updated on February 26, 2015
Learn More
About Wiggy's
The Wiggy's Guarantee
News & Commentary
Popular Topics
Why Lamilite?
General Care Instructions
Temperature Ratings & Sizing
Our Fabrics
Testimonials
Videos
Specials
Our Policies
Shipping & Returns
Ponchos & Poncho Liners
Rain Gear (Waterproof)
Wiggy's Alaska
Base Layers
Marine Wear
Footwear
Boots
Socks, Liners & Booties
Gaiters, Waders & Chaps
Boot & Shoe Laces
Corporate Office & Factory
To place an order, please contact our corporate office & factory at:
Wiggy’s Inc.
PO Box 2124
Grand Junction, CO 81502
+1 (866) 411-6465
f:  (970) 241•5921
e:
Retail Stores
Colorado
2482 Industrial Blvd  •  Grand Junction, CO (970) 241-6465
Alaska
8225 Old Seward Hwy, Ste A  •  Anchorage, AK(907) 336-1330
When it comes to extreme cold weather gear, Wiggy's has you covered.
Check out all our products from sleeping bags & shelters to footwear & clothing. Our uniquely developed continuous filament fiber called Lamilite insulation is what sets Wiggy brand insulated products apart. What is Lamilite and why does it perform better than all other forms of insulation? Click here to keep reading & find out more »
©
Wiggy’s Inc. All Rights Reserved.
All prices are in USD
